OurBigBook.com editing can be done fully on the browser
But you can also edit markup files locally and then upload
We have a Visual Studio Code extension for it
Locally you can have multiple articles per file
and the article tree across files is done with \Include macros
There are two ways to publish from the command line: --web and --publish
ourbigbook --web publishes to ourbigbook.com or another OurBigBook Web instance
ourbigbook.com is a dynamic website, and has multi-user features
such as likes, topics, and discussions
ourbigbook --publish publishes a static website to wherever you want
e.g. here we are publishing to GitHub Pages
A static website is just a bunch of .html files
and can be published easily and cheaply (often free) on many platforms
E.g. cirosantilli.com is a static website hosted on GitHub Pages
and here's our update
You can optionally link from static headers to the dynamic ones to get the best of both worlds
And you can have a split version of each header for better SEO on static renders
it contains just one section on top without child sections
With OurBigBook, you remain in control of your content
with flexible and reliable publishing options to fit your needs